Hello, I am watching Vikas Prapt.
In this video of Technical Vikas, we will
give you information that many people have such a thing that
after making a PF claim, when they
put a request for withdrawal, okay, so here they get a
message in some way, what does this message
mean? Many people have
asked me to send a message and send a screenshot
about this, we will give you information about
why this message comes, what does it mean?
Before starting the video, I will make a small
request, if you have not subscribed to our channel, please
subscribe to the red button Dhaba channel and
press the bell so that you keep getting such updated
information in future also, let's
start the video, here you will see
that dear sir madam your claim ID will
remain under process and will be
settled, that is,
this message has been sent from EPFO
that
when 5 days are over, you put a request, that is, you make a
claim for withdrawal,
okay, I
told you that your claim is still under process here
and soon we will try to settle your claim, that is,
your claim will be settled as soon as possible.  The message does
not mean that your claim will be settled 100%. If
everything is in order, it will be settled.
Otherwise, if for some reason you have some
issue with it, then it can also be rejected.
Suppose the passbook has not been read, there is
some other issue in the passbook, or there is some
other reason, your claim can also be rejected due to that reason.
But most of the times,
you knew that
in most of the cases it does not get settled.
But this is not a guarantee.
Now let's talk about how many days it takes for
your claim to get settled or rejected after receiving such a message. So, your
claim will get settled in a day or two, otherwise it may take
10 days as well, that is,
within two-three days.
I have seen two-three people here,
their claim got settled within two-three days.
After receiving this message, some people's claims were also rejected.
But it does not take much time.
You will see within three-four days that
whatever happens, it will be settled tomorrow.
Or it will be rejected, whatever your status is,
you will get to see it. I hope if you
liked the information, please
like the video and subscribe to the channel.
Your day with the video.